本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
18更多字幕下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
更多字幕下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
■
翻译：  hoRIZon    米小勒    爱吃屎的鱼    顺田小子    泡泡龙    小怡
翻译：  小苗     小样      小Q     大卫熊     奶昔
■
翻译：  毛栗老弟弟     pisces黯淡      shelly      小猴子      小九
时间轴：  小猫     泡泡龙      贝壳     小穗
■
校对：  泡泡龙     米小勒      大卫熊      毛栗老弟弟      小九
后期：   ZWCJY_0908(胖胖)      监制：  米小勒      小九
■
一个舞台  一整个夜晚
准备登台亮相的明星有
Eminem和Mick Jagger
Rihanna和Barbra Streisand
Miranda Lambert和Katy Perry
Usher和Justin Bieber
更多精彩  不容错过
史上最震撼的格莱美颁奖典礼
将掀起众多议论纷纭
今晚的开场  让我们向这位音乐传奇人物
致以最崇高的敬意
灵魂乐女王Aretha Franklin
奖项的获得者  Aretha Franklin
恭喜Aretha Franklin
获奖的是  Aretha Franklin小姐
Aretha Franklin
1975年表演曲目《Ain't Nothin'Like The Real Thing》
1981年表演曲目《Can't Turn You Loose》
1990年表演曲目《Freeway of Love》
1994年表演曲目《Natual Woman》
1998年表演曲目《Respect》
1998年表演曲目《Nessum Dorma》
女士们  先生们
有请两次格莱美奖得主  LL Cool J
Aretha Franklin这位灵魂乐的传奇人物
永恒流传  万年不朽
今晚她是我们心中的传奇女王
是格莱美历史上的传奇女王
她目前为止获得了18项格莱美大奖
Aretha今晚在她底特律的家
进行康复治疗
很遗憾我们的女王今晚没能和我们一起
但诸多才华横溢的音乐家们将同台向女王
致-上-她-们-最-崇-高-的-敬-意
向这位在格莱美的历史中不可或缺的女王致敬
欢迎大家来到第五十三届格莱美现场
在这个意义非凡的夜晚  揭开序幕
我们掌声有请
来自底特律的Greg Phillinganes带领的管弦乐队
还有第一次同台亮相的
Christina Aguilera
Jennifer Hudson
来自Florence and The Machine乐队的Florence Welch
Yolanda Adams和Martina McBride
[歌曲名]"Natual Woman"
女士们  先生们  有请Martina McBride
[歌曲名]《Until You Come Back to Me》
女士们  先生们  有请来自
Florence and The Machine乐队的Florence Welch
[歌曲名]《Think》
女士们  先生们  有请Jennifer Hudson
[歌曲名]《Respect》
(Re, re, re ,re)
[歌名]《Spirit In the Dark》
女士们先生们
有请Yolanda Adams
谢谢女士们  我爱你们
女士们先生们  晚上好
以及各位格莱美获奖歌手们
我无法表达今夜与你们共聚
我的内心是多么的激动
我要在这个特别的时刻
感谢长久以来  这位充满幻想的
格莱美颁奖礼制片人Ken Earlig先生
非常感谢你  Ken
我还要特别感谢所有花时间
送给我康复卡片  鲜花
美丽鲜花的朋友们
也正是你们的祈祷
陪伴了我在院中的治疗时光
我还要感谢Clive Davis先生
对我的关心和为我写的贴心的信
我也希望能跟大家今晚欢聚一堂
但是我今年是来不了了
相约明年如何
致所有的格莱美奖项提名歌手们
祝你们好运
感谢你们  我爱你们
愿今夜过的愉快
第53届格莱美奖接下来的演出
注定成为街知巷闻的谈资
将由Lady GAGA
Bruno Mars  B.O.B以及Janelle Monae
Justin Bieber和Usher
Bob Dylan和Mumford & Sons
以及The Avett Brothers
Cee Lo Green和Gwyneth Paltrow
Eminem和Rihanna以及Dr. Dre
Lady Antebellum
Barbara Streisand
Katy Perry
以及格莱美首次登台的Mick Jagger
第53届格莱美颁奖典礼由
令你美艳动人的封面女郎[彩妆品牌]
以及雪佛兰2011年春季登场的
卡玛罗敞篷跑车倾情赞助
我们一同组团前来
纪念我们心中挚爱的皇后Aretha
那真的是个性感的收尾
我们很荣幸站在这里
颁发今晚第一个格莱美奖项
最佳流行组合演唱奖
下面是提名者
欢乐合唱团  《Don't Stop Believin'》
Maroon5  《Misery》
Paramore  《The Only Exception》
Sade  《Babyfather》
Train  《Hey, Soul Sister》现场版
得奖者是...
我真是有点吓呆了
感谢Justin Bbieber没有入围流行组合演唱奖
我们三人一路经历了很多
很高兴我们能回到这里来
感谢你们过去几年来对我们的支持
感谢这么多人能在我们不自信的时候
依旧坚信我们  支持我们
感谢Jonathan Danile和Bob McLin
挽救了我们的事业
感谢Rob Stringer和Steve Barnett
给了我们又一次机会
感谢Lisa Sankin  John Boris  Jim Burris
以及哥伦比亚公司的每个朋友
天呐  要感谢好多人
感谢Jim和Greg Watenberg以及
所有制作这张专辑的人  感谢所有人
真的很感谢你们
现在换Howard来说
感谢我们的粉丝
女士们先生们  掌声欢迎
格莱美奖得主  Ricky Martin
去年  她与Elton John先生
为格莱美献上了一场华丽的开场秀
并抱走了两项格莱美大奖
今晚她准备好赢得另一项格莱美奖
她要与大家分享一首很有意义的歌
这首歌鼓励人们勇敢去爱
并坚持做你自己
这是她首次现场演唱她的新单曲
《Born This Way》
有请Lady Gaga
大家一起来
即将呈现
更多精彩的格莱美现场表演
包括Miranda Lambert  Muse
Bruno Mars与
B.O.B和Janelle Mona的强强联手
Justin Bierber与
Usher和Jahen Smith同台献唱
更晚些  还将有Bob Dylan
Lady Antebellum
Cee Lo Green
与Gwyneth Paltrow的联手合唱
Katy Perry
还有Rihanna  Dr.Dre与
获本届格莱美十项提名的Eminem携手
为您献上难忘的表演
精彩尽在YYeTs
格莱美的粉丝们
确定自己认真看了今晚的节目吗
你可以"走走瞧瞧"YYeTs.com网站
只要你看到这枚标志
回答关于节目的问题
就有机会成为明年格莱美的观众
女士们  先生们
掌声有请Blake Shelton
当我说我爱下一位出场的歌手
我的意思是我真的爱这位歌手
她不仅是世界上最有才华的女人
她还正好是我的未婚妻
哥老给力了
女士们  先生们
下面这首歌《The house that built me》
获得今晚的两项年度歌曲提名
有请最美丽  最有才
最独一无二的Miranda Lambert
今晚我演唱的这首歌
要献给所有优秀的艺术家前辈
他们为我们铺设了今天的这个舞台
造就了今天的我们
有请四次获得格莱美奖的Lenny Kravitz
有的乐队开场演唱会
在场的人会纷纷起立喝彩
下面这个乐队
每次占据舞台都会出现如此盛况
请起立欢迎过去几年叱咤世界
今晚获得三项提名
在格莱美舞台上初次亮相的
独一无二的英国Muse乐队
我是Ellen K  在格莱美颁奖典礼的后台
正如刚刚你所看到的
Muse的摇滚棒极了
即将看到的是  情歌三重唱
来自才华横溢年轻有为的
Bruno Mars  B.O.B.和Janelle Monae
之后有Justin Bieber
与Usher以及Jaden Smith的同台表演
Bob Dylan和The Avett Brothers
以及Mumford & Sons的强强联手
还将看到Lady Antebellum
Cee Lo Green与Gwyneth Paltrow以及几位
我们非常熟悉的毛茸茸的朋友的演唱
Eminem联手Rihanna还有Dr. Dre
Mick Jagger
Barbra Streisand
一切尽在第五十三届格莱美颁奖礼
锁定YYeTs
第五十三届格莱美颁奖礼的赞助商有
Target[美国第二大百货公司]
期盼多多付出少少
全新福特探险家牌越野车
开一辆回家吧
有请Ryan Seacrest
今晚我们见证了很多音乐神话
但是音乐总是需要新声音
而此刻  我们要史无前例的
呈献给大家一曲由年轻有为才华横溢
的新星们所带来的三重唱
他们三位一共获得了14项格莱美提名
其中一位今晚已经抱得一座奖杯
就在这里
机不可失 时不再来
就在格莱美
有请Bruno Mars  B.O.B.以及Janelle Monae
女士们先生们
准备好继续灵魂乐串烧了吗
我也准备好了
接下来出场的这个小伙
专门为了今晚的颁奖典礼而来
我就不费口舌了
掌声有请我们的老朋友
Bruno Mars先生
谢谢大家
我想借此机会
向大家介绍一位
我深爱的女孩
你懂什么是爱
我觉得我心都碎了
我想和她永远在一起
我问她愿意吗
你们知道她怎么回答的吗
她怎么回答
我就知道
我都告诉她  她很漂亮了
她还是不愿意
但我傻乎乎的还深爱着她
如果今天她站在这里
亲爱的我就在这里等着你
跟我一起回家吧
表演还要继续
大家起立欢迎
我的好友Janelle Monae女士
我要飞下去了
有请两项格莱美提名者
Dierks Bentley
以及已赢得一个奖项的
Zac Brown
颁发下一个奖项之前
Zac和我想先感谢全世界的粉丝们
感谢在场与不在场的每一个人
伟大的乡村音乐作曲家
Harlan Howard曾说过
乡村音乐三弦内现真情
接下来这五位女士
都将真情体现的淋漓尽致
获得最佳乡村女歌手演唱提名的有
《Satisfied》  Jewel
《The House That Built Me》  Miranda Lambert
《Swingin》  LeAnn Rimes
《Temporary Home》  Carrie Underwood
《I'd Love To Be Your Last》 Gretchen Wilson
获得格莱美奖的是
《The House That Built Me》  Miranda Lambert
首度荣获这个格莱美演唱奖
有史以来首个格莱美奖
感谢Tom和Ellen写了这么美的一首歌
感谢大家喜欢这首歌的歌词
这对我来说意味着一切
每个人都能感同身受
我还要感谢Moria Crafting和Joey Lee
以及我的乐队On The Road
以及所有鼓励我的人
还有在座的每位嘉宾  十分感谢
我大爱乡村音乐
稍后继续
Justin Bieber及其导师Usher
携手Jaden Smith
Bob Dylan携手Mumford & Sons
以及The Avett Brothers登台献艺
随后表演的是Lady Antebellum
Cee-Lo Green以及Gwyneth Paltrow
Katy Perry
Eminem  Rihanna和Dr. Dre三人同台
Barbra Streisand
Mick Jagger
以及Arcade Fire首度登台格莱美
精彩尽在YYeTs
女士们先生们
掌声有请Eva Longoria
在2007年一位满怀梦想的加拿大男孩
来到了佐治亚州亚特兰大
在停车场  他巧遇一位乐坛巨星
这孩子说愿意为他歌唱
从此开启了一段师徒关系
如今他们都跻身乐坛巨星
今晚各自两度提名
幸运的是  这是21世纪
所有伟大时刻都被纪录
让我们穿越到2007
回顾那场值得纪念的事件
即今晚最佳新人奖提名者
当时年仅13岁的Justin Bieber
巧遇今晚已获奖的Usher
棒极了
简直不敢置信
没错  四年前的
- 就是这么开始的  对吧  - 是啊
但他们没说准到底是怎么回事
我在停车场遇见你
- 但你一开始没唱给我听  - 没有
然后我跟你说了些事你才唱的
你告诉我
如果成功  我们会再次相见
没错  现在该你表演了
开始吧
有请今晚获得格莱美提名的Paramore
和《海军罪案调查》主演Pauley Perrette
我不知道哪件事更让我兴奋
是宣布格莱美最佳摇滚专辑获得者
还是能和Paramore待一分钟
很高兴能和你一起颁奖
获得这一奖项提名的
都是久负盛名的摇滚天才
有两支美国摇滚乐队
还有今晚已经掀起一阵高潮的英国组合
下面是最佳摇滚专辑提名
《Emotion & Commotion》  Jeff Beck
《The Resistance》  Muse
《Backspacer》  Pearl Jam
《Mojo》  Tom Petty & The Heartbreakers
《Le Noise》  Neil Young
获奖的是...
《The Resistance》  Muse
非常感谢
真是个巨大的惊喜
很荣幸能和今晚表演的
这么多优秀歌手齐聚一堂
每一个得奖的人都是实至名归
我要感谢我们的经纪人Keu Punt
他在美国给予了我们很多帮助
还要特别感谢那边我的已怀身孕的女友
你说两句
很高兴能来这儿
非常感谢格莱美
很荣幸能获奖
真的很荣幸
非常感谢为我投票的业界专家
让我们能获此殊荣
谢谢我们的歌迷
大家欢呼吧  谢谢你们
访问grammy.com查询完全获奖名单
下载今晚精彩绝伦的表演
还有格莱美现场独家幕后消息
还可以关注Twitter  Facebook和Youtube
上发布的格莱美最新消息
接下来有
Bob Dylan 携Mumford & Sons
和The Avett Brothers带来的表演
Lady Antebellum
Cee Lo Green  和Gwyneth Paltrow
Katy Perry带来的"Teenage Dream"
Eminem不仅会与Rihanna共同演出
还将和Dr. Dre来一场意义重大的合作
Mick Jagger在格莱美舞台上首次亮相
Barbra Streisand
和Arcade Fire
精彩格莱美  尽在YYeTs
有请Selena Gomez
以及《警察世家》主演
来自"新街边男孩"组合的Donnie Wahlberg
从Susan Boyle到Justin Bieber
今年最佳流行演唱专辑的提名名单
绝对算是年龄跨度极大
Ray Charles Joni Mitchell
Sade 和Justin Timberlake
都曾获得此奖项
《My World 2.0》  Justin Bieber
《I Dreamed A Dream》  Susan Boyle
《The Fame Monster》  Lady Gaga
《Battle Studies》  John Mayer
《Teenage Dream》  Katy Perry
得奖的是...
《The Fame Monster》  Lady Gaga
我从心底感谢你们
我所有的歌迷们
所有见证我得奖的怪物们[Gaga的歌迷]
感谢我的父母
和我美丽的妹妹Natalie
我爱你们
感谢Vincent和Troy对我的支持
你们是最好的经纪人
和最赞的拍档
谢谢Jimmy Ivene
谢谢Doug Lawrence的帮助
谢谢Interscope公司的整个团队
在我很小的时候我就梦想着
能成为自己想成为的人
不管我想象中的自己是什么样子
不管有没有人相信我能成功
非常谢谢你们  谢谢
今晚我要对Whitney Houston说声谢谢
我之所以要谢谢她是因为
当我写《Born This Way》时
我想象的是她在唱这首歌
因为我当时并没有足够的自信
所以就把自己想象成超级巨星
所以  Whitney  我写《Born This Way》时
想象的是你在演唱
谢谢你
下面是2011年格莱美十大惊喜
第十的是
Lindsay Lohan被看到以格莱美体型的身材
穿着外套离开了史泰博体育中心
第九  最新的音乐法规定
禁止将"Ladies"和"Mercedes"押韵
这是个好主意  我喜欢
第八  Willie Nelson给格莱美表演
带来了点"小吃"
第七  Jay-Z揭露"Empire State Of Mind"
指的其实是塔伦顿[新泽西首府]  没错
第六  今年新增奖项  叫做男女传统R&B
城市音乐/另类音乐  非古典工程
拉丁  流行组合演唱大奖
第五  在这个感人的典礼中
Will.I.Am在名字后面又加了个逗号
第四  学院主席终于解释了
年度最佳专辑和年度最佳歌曲的区别
第三  Lady Antebellum 和Lady Gaga
组成了一个超级组合Lady Antegagum
第二  John Mayer和Susan Boyle
热情拥抱
2011格莱美颁奖礼最大的惊喜是
Justin Bieber戴的是假发
女士们先生们
下面是Mumford & Sons  The Avett Brothers
和特别来宾Bob Dylan的表演
有请Avett Brothers
女士们先生们  有请Bob Dylan
这是格莱美独有的景象
Mumford & Sons  Avett Brothers和Bob Dylan
同台演出
即将呈现  Lady Antebellum
Cee Lo Green与Gwyneth Paltrow
Katy Perry
Eminem与Rihanna  以及Dr.Dre
Mick Jagger的格莱美处女秀
Barbra Streisand
以及格莱美新星Arcade Fire
还有年度制作和专辑奖
第五十三届格莱美奖精彩看点
尽在YYeTs
今年美国音乐学院终身成就奖的提名者是
音乐界和演艺界双栖明星Julie Andrews
Acclaimed Jazz鼓手兼领队Roy Haynes
古典音乐常青树组合Julliard String Quartet
民歌复兴组合Kingston Trio
乡村歌手兼作曲  超级巨星Dolly Parton
朋克摇滚先驱The Ramones
深受全美爱戴的福音歌手George Beverly Shea
学院授予以上所有歌手终身成就奖
《欢乐合唱团》的明星代表
以及超级碗冠军"绿湾包装工"球队成员
Lea Michele和Clay Matthews
Clay  超级碗冠军感觉如何
不可思议  Lea
好像活在梦境中
我们深知这一点
下面登场的乐队
度过了梦幻般的一年
向我们伟大的灵魂乐歌手
去年离我们而去的Teddy Pendergrass致敬
同时还会带来他们自己的热门曲目
今晚已包揽两座格莱美奖杯的
Lady Antebellum
热烈欢迎Miley Cyrus和Kings Of Leon
我跟Kings的成员们都来自
我们乡村音乐的发源地  田纳西州
因此我们十分荣幸能够颁出下一个奖项
获得最佳乡村专辑提名的有
"Up On The Ridge"  Dierks Bentley
"You Get What You Give"  Zac Brown Band
"The Guitar Song"  Jamey Johnson
"Need You Now"  Lady Antebellum
"Revolution"  Miranda Lambert
获得格莱美奖的是
Lady Antebellum的"Need You Now"
喔天呐
嗨Paul Worley
天呐  我们想要先感谢我们的唱片公司
感谢百代这一年里帮我们获得了这么大的成功
感谢上帝  还有我们家中的亲友们
感谢你们给予在外拼搏的我们莫大的支持
还有Paul Worley  我们的制作人
感谢与我们一路走来的Clark  我们的策划
才华横溢的音乐家
我就不逐个点名了
要感谢的太多  我记不住的
谢谢你们  乡村乐广播台  我们爱你
欢迎格莱美与奥斯卡得主Jamie Foxx
他的新专辑名叫"Best Night Of My Life"
怎么样  大家都怎么样
今晚本来没我什么事
电视台非求我颁这个奖的时候
别说啥不合时宜的字眼
切  要我说
我非说...靠...一边去吧
这里是美国对不对
来  都叫出声来
我就寻思吧
让他们靠...一边儿凉快去吧
靠得嘞  我说得对不
好了  接下来让我们欣赏"Forget You"
这首歌不但获得年度歌曲与年度制作提名
由奥斯卡得主Gwyneth Paltrow与五颜六色的木偶参与演出
今晚格莱美奖得主
一起为Cee-Lo Green疯狂吧
一起来  跟我唱
接下来  还有Katy Perry的表演
Keith Urban  Norah Jones和John Mayer
颁发年度歌曲奖
之后Eminem与Rihanna和Dr. Dre一同表演
谁会是最佳新人的得奖者呢
接下来还有Mick Jagger向灵魂乐大师致敬
现今很少见的Barbra Streisand现场表演
还有Arcade Fire格莱美首演
谁会夺走年度专辑和年度制作大奖
敬请关注YYeTs
第53届格莱美颁奖
为您提供明星的独家物品和VIP体验
明星包括Eminem  Jay-Z  Ke$ha
Lady Gaga  Slash  Britney Spears
Barbra Streisand  Train和多位今晚的明星
请参与格莱美慈善eBay竞拍
帮助音乐关怀基金会和格莱美基金会
请登录cbs.com查询
活动由玉兰油赞助  挑战一切可能
女士们  先生们  艾美奖得主
剧集《老爸老妈恋爱史》
和新片《新美女与野兽》主演Neil Patrick Harris
哟哟哟
下一位表演嘉宾是火辣的超级明星
她将于下周开始世界巡演
上个周一  我有幸跟她上了床
[Katy客串了Neil主演的《老爸老妈浪漫史》]
当然是在电视上
我得说她让我精疲力尽  性欲十足
又困惑不已
她今晚有四项提名  包括年度专辑奖
女士们  先生们
有请Katy Perry
这首歌送给所有的情人们
和我一起唱
女士们先生们  有请
格莱美得主三人组
Norah Jones  John Mayer和
刚刚得奖的Keith Urban
我们唱这首歌是为了
向一位伟大的艺人  词曲作者致敬
她是今年终身成就奖获得者
传奇一般的Dolly Parton
我们爱你  Dolly
现在我们很荣幸的为大家颁发年度歌曲奖
这个奖项03年的获奖歌曲是Norah Jones的"Don't Know Why"
这个奖项05年的获奖歌曲是John的"Daughters"
我们记得
- 歌名叫"Daughters"  不是女儿  - 对
我照本宣科  这是过去的一年我们记住的歌曲
获得年度歌曲提名的有
由Ray LaMontagne创作的"Beg Steal Or Borrow"
演唱者  Ray Lamontagne和The Pariah Dogs
由Brody Brown  Cee Lo Green  Philip Lawrence  Ari Levine
和Bruno Mars联合创作的"Fuck you"(亦作"Forget you")
演唱者  Cee Lo Green
由Tom Douglas和Allen Shamblin联合创作的"The House That Built Me"
演唱者  Miranda Lambert
有Alexander Grant  Skylar Grey
和Marshall Mathers联合创作的"Love The Way You Lie"
演唱者  Eminem和Rihanna
由Dave Haywood  Josh Kear  Charles Kelley
和Hillary Scott联合创作的"Need You Now"
演唱者  Lady Antebellum
获得格莱美年度歌曲的是
由Dave Haywood  Josh Kear  Charles Kelley和Hillary Scott创作
Lady Antebellum演唱的"Need You Now"
真是令人惊喜的一年
我们太开心了
感谢上帝
感谢身在纳什维尔和乔治亚州的亲戚朋友
感谢伯曼唱片公司的员工
是啊  感谢Gary Boreman
是你给这首歌大红大紫
改变了我们的一生  谢谢
Josh  你来说
感谢我的夫人
感谢喜欢这首歌的歌迷们
当然  也要感谢你们仨
老婆  谢谢你  情人节快乐
爱你们
感谢歌迷
感谢广播电台
去年我们的生活发生了天翻地覆的变化
我们非常爱你们  谢谢
接下来  Eminem将与Rihanna共同演绎嘻哈传说
并将在舞台上与Dr. Dre重聚
Justin Bieber能否一举击败大哥哥大姐姐
Drake  Florence & The Machine  Mumford & Sons
和Esperanza Spalding获得最佳新人奖吗
2011年格莱美音乐提名专辑现已发售
专辑的部分收入将投入格莱美基金会
为音乐教育竭尽所能  在塔吉特超市有售
欢迎即将上映的电影《保罗》中的Seth Rogen
大家好
这是我首次来到格莱美颁奖现场
目前为止玩得很开心
很多前所未见  前所未闻的事让我大开眼界
当然我指的不是直播现场
我是说我和Miley Cyrus还后台嗨起来了
[影射Miley吸大麻事件]
说出来还别不相信
让我介绍这位嘻哈史上最邪魅狷狂的歌手再合适不过了
跟他同台的有Adam Levine和Skyler Grey
欢迎三位巨星Rihanna  Dr. Dre和今晚两项大奖
得主Eminem
掌声有请今晚的提名歌手Jewel
以及今天又将三项格莱美收入囊中的John Legend
我和John都深知
格莱美最佳新人提名是一项至高荣誉
对一个看着格莱美长大的人来说
赢得最佳新人奖意味着梦想成真
我们来见证此刻谁将实现梦想
请看最佳新人提名
Justin Bieber
Drake
Florence & The Machine
Mumford & Sons
Esperanza Spalding
获得格莱美最佳新人奖的是
祝贺你
我知道时间有限
那么首先  感谢美国音乐学院
在这个奖项中提名我
感谢无与伦比的社区音乐家们
我有幸能成为你们中的一员
感谢我在波特兰的朋友  老师和同事
还有我幸福的一家人
尤其是Gill Goldsteen
Joe  Daniel  Dan Halis  Dave love
Mark Wexler  John Burke
感谢我优秀的朋友们
我由衷地感谢这份荣誉
我会尽最大努力
为你们献上更多伟大的音乐
这是一份无上殊荣
感谢上帝
感谢大家
最佳新人奖颁出后
我们将迎来摇滚史上最富盛名的歌手
Mick Jagger首次登上格莱美舞台
带来一份特别的演出
随后  八座格莱美奖得主
Barbra Streisand也将倾情献唱
Rihanna联袂Drake
Arcade Fire初登格莱美舞台
以及年度专辑和年度制作的颁发
第53届格莱美颁奖典礼
精彩尽在YYeTs
第53届格莱美由以下品牌赞助
全新雪佛兰沃特
北美地区2011年度最佳车系
以及惠普产品
方便个人互联
女士们先生们
有请《欢乐合唱团》的一位明星
即将推出首张专辑的Matthew Morrison
小时候  我一直梦想站上格莱美的舞台
今晚  梦想成为现实
我已成为音乐学院的成员
现在我知道  除去颁发格莱美奖
他们还做过许多伟大业绩
这些工作深得我心
为了让你们更好地了解
也为了我明年能重返这个舞台
我很荣幸为大家请出
音乐学院的主席兼执行总裁
也是我的好朋友
Neil Portnow先生
感谢Matthew
继续你那有意义的工作
我们今晚欢庆格莱美年度盛会
而音乐学院则一直关注着未来
我们的格莱美基金会
为全国各地的中学音乐教育提供赞助
今年  格莱美夏令营
冲出洛杉矶  增加了纽约之旅
登录grammyintheschools.com并提出申请
世事难料
也许有一天你也能登上格莱美舞台
可以看到  音乐的未来一片光明
我们掌声欢迎今晚的最佳新人得主
Esperanza Spalding
以及来自格莱美爵士乐团
和格莱美夏令营乐团的
优秀中学生音乐家
也许我在剧中扮演了音乐教师
但是培养下一代才华横溢的音乐人
是我和学院的共同目标
我们的音乐关怀基金将继续其慈善任务
在危机中帮助每个有需要的人
包括戒毒康复
我们的第二十届年度宣传活动
今年共筹集资金一千万美元
我们位于洛杉矶的格莱美博物馆
已经成为当今音乐界
最具娱乐性的一大文化和教育中心
看看吧
我很荣幸成为博物馆的一员
人人都有机会参与
它给我提供一个伟大契机
了解音乐的历史
以及我们今日的努力方向
这家伙我没看走眼
大家放心  今后
音乐学院将继续确保所有音乐人
都能够劳有所获
我们会赞助新型的播送服务
例如卫星和网络电台
让他们得到应得的回报
通过这些便捷合法的途径来享受音乐
您将帮助音乐人创造您喜爱的音乐
我们也将继续支持音乐人的言论自由
让他们通过音乐表达自身
我愿代表音乐学院承认对David Geffen的表彰
他于昨晚获得音乐学院的产业偶像奖
祝贺你  David
[音乐学院产业偶像奖]
还有一件事
在当今世界最严重的一次经济衰退中
有一样东西未曾改变
你们可以坚信
我们这个富有创造力的团体
从未改变过自己的承诺和决心
我们将永不放弃音乐
我们展望未来之时  不要忘记
在过去的一年里
我们失去了一些乐坛精英
让我们暂停此刻  共同追忆他们
[缅怀]
今晚我很高兴来到这里
来到这座美妙的城市
我要向Salomon Burke致敬
大家一起喊"Yeah"
我听到你们了
大家开心吗
大家真的开心吗
来啊
大家一起来
谢谢
谢谢大家
[理事奖]
美国音乐学院设置的理事奖
是为表彰那些在音像领域
做出非表演性质突出贡献的个人
今年  这一奖项将授予
格莱美奖得主  古典音乐制作人
已故的Wilma Cozart Fine
以及两位业绩出众的
资深唱片制作执行主管
Al Bell  他与史塔克斯  魔城
和贝尔马克均有合作
以及Bruce Lundvall
他曾效力于哥伦比亚
艾丽卡  曼哈顿和蓝调唱片公司
女士们  先生们
让我们有请三度获得格莱美奖的
Kris Kristofferson
接下来这位美丽的天才歌手
可谓闻君一曲  养性怡情
她有着天籁般的嗓音和冠军之心
却又褒有孩童般的狡黠
作为一名演员  导演兼制作人
和一位人道主义者
她以她纯净的灵魂和歌声
抚慰了我们生之苦痛
我们将要听到的这首歌
曾获奥斯卡和格莱美年度歌曲奖
让我们有请
有史以来最有才华的一位乐坛巨星
音乐关怀年度人物得主  Barbra Streisand
掌声有请Nicki Minaj和Will.I.Am
自格莱美最佳说唱专辑奖创立以来
该奖就一直眷顾改变音乐史走向的歌手
这些杰出人物包括Outkast
Kanye West和Li'l Wayne
还有今晚再获提名的
Jay-Z与Eminem
最佳说唱专辑奖的提名专辑有
《The Adventures Of Bobby Ray》B.o.B
《Thank Me Later》Drake
《Recovery》Eminem
《The Blueprint 3》Jay-Z
《How I Got Over》The Roots
获得格莱美奖的是
Eminem的《Recovery》
这太疯狂了
谢谢
首先  我想说  感谢每一个人
所有帮助我出这张专辑的制作人
所有人都至关重要  专辑所有的制作人
我还想感谢Rihanna
是她将此张专辑提升到这个高度
感谢环球唱片公司
感谢Dr. Dre  Paul Rosenberg
Jimmy Elvine  Tracy McNew  Mark Labell
每一位  Shady Aftermath这个大家庭
环球唱片公司  谢谢
感谢我的歌迷
你们好吗  底特律  加油
登录grammy.com  查看所有获奖者
下载今晚的精彩表演
还有独家奉送的格莱美现场花絮
在Twitter  Facebook和Youtube上
查看格莱美奖
下节预告  Rihanna与Drake同台表演
Arcade Fire首次亮相格莱美
谁将赢得今晚最受瞩目的两项大奖
年度制作和年度专辑奖
2011年度格莱美专辑正在热销
部分专辑获利将捐赠给格莱美基金会
以促进音乐教育事业的发展
详情尽在grammy.com
有请三座格莱美奖获得者Puff Daddy
她是音乐界最持之以恒的一位歌手
而他是最有才华的说唱歌手之一
他们将
共同演绎
他们的火爆单曲
有请今晚的获奖歌手
Rihanna与Drake现场表演"What's My Name"
女士们  先生们
有请Jennifer Lopez和Marc Anthony
好了  一些最有名的音乐经典
都曾获得过此奖项
首个格莱美年度制作奖是
Volare, oooh
我爸爸有这张专辑
从那时起
一些最为经久不衰的大作
得到了这项格莱美奖
从"Moon River"
-  Moon River   - 老天
"Bridge Over Troubled Waters"
- 是这么唱的  -到"Beat it"等等
- 好吧  - 好
获得年度制作奖提名的歌曲有
"Nothin' On You" B.o.B和Bruno Mars
"Love The Way You Lie" Eminem和Rihanna
别名"Forget You" Cee Lo Green
"Empire State Of Mind" Jay-Z和Alicia Keys
"Need You Now" Lady Antebellum
获奖的是
恭喜你们
我的天哪
我挡着你呢
真是太意外了
我们开始都走错方向了
非常感谢美国音乐学院
你们要知道今年对我们的重要性
我们去年就有机会
在格莱美这个舞台演唱这首歌
这一年意义重大
我们感激不尽
难以置信
我们在后台痛哭流涕
我不敢相信我们会再次站到这个舞台上
Clark  说点什么吧  兄弟
我要感谢Lady A
还要感谢Paul
你们太棒了
大家做的很好不过还要再接再厉
谢谢大家
这里是格莱美之夜  精彩还在继续
不要走开
第五十三届格莱美奖颁奖盛典
还有更多精彩表演
Arcade Fire将首次在格莱美表演
年度专辑奖也将揭晓
不要转台  敬请期待CBS
第五十三届格莱美奖颁奖盛典
高中生们
和格莱美在洛城或纽约共度盛夏
申请格莱美夏令营
请登录www.grammyintheschools.com
品牌赞助
焕然一新  百分百全新设计福特探索者
拥有一辆吧
还有塔吉特
期待更多  花费更少
女士们  先生们
欢迎《老爸老妈浪漫史》中的演员
Jason Segel
欢迎来到格莱美
今晚即证明了音乐最重要的是什么
如果你是个名利双收的人
那你想穿什么就穿什么
我12岁之前在学校都穿超人披风
我每天都被痛打
我的绰号叫Lady Gaga
但那是20年前的事了
我们得成熟点了
就这样
当我知道要来请出下面这支乐队时
我真的被震撼了
那么女士们  先生们
有请Arcade Fire
接下来  两位明星将重新聚首
颁发年度专辑奖
今晚最后的奖项花落谁家呢
Arcade Fire
Eminem
Lady Antebellum
Lady Gaga
还是Katy Perry
精彩尽在CBS电视台
久别重逢
Barbra Streisand和Kris Kristofferson
现在  大家期待已久的
年度专辑奖的提名
《The Suburbs》 Arcade Fire
《Recovery》 Eminem
《Need You Now》 Lady Antebellum
《The Fame Monster》 Lady Gaga
《Teenage Dream》 Katy Perry
获奖的是
《The Suburbs》 Arcade Fire
谢谢
感谢蒙特利尔和魁北克
给了我们一个家
给了乐队一个生存之地
感谢你们大家
谢谢  我们还要表演一首曲目
因为我们热爱音乐
谢谢格莱美
谢谢你们大家  我们感激涕零
晚安大家
谢谢你们  爸爸妈妈
再见  其他的感谢一并融在歌中  谢谢
格莱美20年官方酒店希尔顿酒店
荣誉支持格莱美委员会推进音乐事业
达美航空遍及6个大陆的350个城市
送您轻松抵达全球
查询航班信息  登陆delta.com
达美航班  一路前行
唱片由国国家录音艺术与科学学会
及唱片公司送评
之后由学会的一万两千名成员独立决出
他们都是唱片业界人员
第一轮投票决出提名
第二轮投票决出获奖者
两轮投票结果均由德勤会计公司制表
Looking out on the morning rain
I used to feel uninspired
And when I knew I had to face another day
Lord, it made me feel so tired
Before the day I met you life was so unkind
But your love was the key to peace my mind
Cause you make me feel
You make me feel
You make me feel like
A natural woman (Woman)
Ain't no way
Ain't no way for me to love you
If you won't let me
Oh, but how can I, how can I, how can I
Give you all the things
If you're tying both of my hands
Oh, it ain't no way
Ain't no way
It ain't no way
It just ain't no way, baby
Ain't no way
Ain't no way, baby
For me to love you
If you won't let me
Baby baby baby
Ain't no way
Ain't no way, baby
For me to love you
I sit and wait in vain
I guess I'll rap on your door
Tap on your window pane
I wanna tell you, baby
Changes I've been going through
Missing you, missing you
Til you come back to me
That's what I'm gonna do
Till you come back to me
That's
What I'm
Gonna
Do
Think about what you're trying to do to me
Yeah, think (think, think)
Let your mind go, let yourself be free
Let's go back, let's go back
Let's go way back when
I didn't even know you
You couldn't have been too much more than ten
(Just a child)
I ain't no psychiatrist
I ain't no doctor with degree
It don't take too much high IQ's
To see what you're trying to do to me
Yeah, you better think
Think what you're trying to do to me
Think
Let your mind go, let yourself be free
Oh freedom (freedom), freedom (freedom)
Freedom, yeah freedom
Freedom (freedom), freedom (freedom)
Freedom, oh freedom
What you want
Baby, I got
What you need
Do you know I got it
All I'm askin'
Is for a little respect when you come home
(Just a little bit)
Hey baby (just a little bit)
When you get home
(Just a little bit) mister
(Just a little bit)
Ooo, your kisses
Sweeter than honey
And guess what
So is my money
And all I want you to do for me
Is give it to me
When you get home
Yeah baby
(Respect, just a little bit)
When you get home, now (just a little bit)
R-E-S-P-E-C-T
Find out what it means to me
Take care, TCB
Oh (Sock it to me)
A little respect
I get tired
Keep on tryin'
Your're running out of food
And I ain't lying
Hey, I'm getting the spirit
In the dark
I'm getting the spirit
People moving
Aw, ain't we groovin
Cause I give it the spirit
In the dark (in the dark)
It's like sally walker
Sittin' in a saucer
That's how ya do it
Now, get on up to it
Rise, sally, rise
Put your hands in the air
And cover your eyes
So just move
In the spirit
Hey move
Hey in the spirit
So let it go yeah yeah yeah yeah
Now, there was a time
When they used to say
That behind every
Great man
There had to be
A great woman
But all in these times of change
You know that it's
No longer true
So we're comin' out of the kitchen
Cause there's somethin'we forgot to say to you
We say sisters are doin' it
For themselves
Standin' on
Their own two feet
And ringin' on their own bells
Sisters are doin' it for themselves
Now, we ain't makin' stories
And we ain't layin' plans
Cause a man still loves a woman
And a woman still loves a man
Just the same
Sisters are doin' it for themselves
Standin' on their own two feet
And ringin' on their own bells
Sisters are doin' it for themselves
One more time
Sisters are doin' it for
Themselves
It doesn't matter if you love him
Or capital h-i-m
Just put your paws up
'Cause you were born this way, baby
My mama told me when I was young
We are all born superstars
She rolled my hair and put my lipstick on
In the glass of her boudoir
"There's nothin wrong with lovin who you are"
She said, "'cause he made you perfect, babe"
So hold your head up girl
And you'll go far,
Listen to me when I say"
I'm beautiful in my way
'Cause god makes no mistakes
I'm on the right track baby
I was born this way
Don't hide yourself in regret
Just love yourself and you're set
I'm on the right track baby
I was born this way
Ooo there ain't no other way
Baby I was born this way
Born this way
Ooo there ain't no other way
I'm on the right track baby
I was born this way
Don't be a drag
Just be a queen
Don't be
Give yourself prudence
And love your friends
Subway kid, rejoice your truth
In the religion of the insecure
I must be myself, respect my youth
A different lover is not a sin
Believe capital h-i-m
Hey hey hey
I love my life I love this record
And mi amore vole fe yah
I'm beautiful in my way
'Cause god makes no mistakes
I'm on the right track baby
I was born this way
Don't hide yourself in regret
Just love yourself and you're set
I'm on the right track baby
I was born this way
Ooo there ain't no other way
Baby I was born this way
Born this way
Ooo there ain't no other way
I'm on the right track baby
Baby I was born this way
Don't be
Don't be a drag
Just be a queen
Whether you're broke or evergreen
You're black, white, beige，chola descent
You're lebanese
You're orient
Whether life's disabilities
Left you outcast
Bullied or teased
Rejoice and love yourself today
'Cause baby you were born this way
No matter gay, straight, or bi
Lesbian, transgendered life
I'm on the right track, baby
I was born to survive
Survive
Ooo there ain't no other way
Baby I was born this way
I was born this way
Right track, baby
I was born this way hey
I'm on the right track, baby
I know they say
You can't go home again
I just had to come back one last time
Ma'am I know
You don't know me from Adam
But these handprints
On the front steps are mine
Up those stairs
In that little back bedroom
Is where I did my homework
And I learned to play guitar
I bet you didn't know
Under that live oak
My favorite dog is buried in the yard
I thought if I could touch this place or feel it
This brokenness inside me might start healing
Out here it's like I'm someone else
I thought that maybe I could find myself
If I could just come in I swear I'll leave
Won't take nothing but a memory
From the house that built me
Mama cut out pictures
Of houses for years
From Better Homes
And Gardens magazine
Plans were drawn and concrete poured
Nail by nail and board by board
Daddy gave life to mama's dream
I thought if I could touch this place or feel it
This brokenness inside me might start healing
Out here it's like I'm someone else
I thought that maybe
I could find myself
If I could just come in
I swear I'll leave
Won't take nothing but a memory
From the house that built me
You leave home
And move on
You do the best you can
I got lost in this old world
And forgot who I am
I thought if I could
Touch this place or feel it
This brokenness inside me
Might start healing
Out here
It's like I'm someone else
I thought that maybe
I could find myself
If I could walk around
I swear I'll leave
Won't take nothing but a memory
From the house that built me
Paranoia is in bloom
The P.R. Transmissions
Will resume
They'll try to push drugs
That keep us all dumbed down
And hope that we will
Never see the truth around
So come on
Another promise, another seed
Another packaged lie
To keep us trapped in greed
And all the green belts
Wrapped around our minds
And endless red tape
To keep the truth confined
So come on
They will not
Force us
They will stop
Degrading us
They will not
Control us
We will
Be victorious
So come on
Interchanging mind control
Come let the revolution
Take its toll
If you could flick the switch
And open your third eye
You'd see that we should
Never be afraid to die
So come on
Rise up and take the power back
It's time the fat cats
Had a heart attack
You know that their time has
Come to an end
We have to unify
And watch our flag ascend
So come on
They will not
Force us
They will stop
Degrading us
They will not
Control us
We will
Be victorious
So come on
They will not
Force us
They will stop
Degrading us
They will not
Control us
We will
Be victorious
Beautiful Girls
All over the world
I could be chasing
But my time would be wasted
They got nothing on you, baby
Nothing on you, baby
I know you feel where I'm coming from
Regardles of the things in my past that I've done
Most of really was for the hell of the fun
On the carousel so around I spun
With no directions just trying to get some
Trying to chase skirts living in the summer sun
So I lost more than I had ever won
And honestly
I ended up with none
There's no much nonsense
It's on my conscience
I'm thinking, baby I should get it out
And I don't want to sound redundant
But I was wondering
That there's something that you want to know
But never mind
That we should let it go
'Cause we don't want to be a TV episode
And all the bad thought just let them go
Go, go
Beautifu girls
All over the world
I could be chasing
But my time would be wasted
They got noghing on you
Not, not, not nothing on you, baby
Not. not nothing on you
Nothing on you
Not, not, not nothing on you, baby
Not, not nothing on you
They might say hi
And I might say hey
But you shouldn't worry
About what they say
Cause they got nothing on you
Not, not, not nothing on you, baby
Not, not nothing on you
Nothing on you baby
Not, not, not nothing on you, baby
Not. not nothing on you
Everywhere I go
I'm always hering your name
And no maater where I'm at
Girl, you make me want to sing
Whether a bus or a plane
Or a car or a train
No other girl's in my brain
And you the one to blame
This is what I'd tell her
This is what I'd say
I'd get down on my knees
And tell her that I'd
I'd, I'd
Catch a grenade for you
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Throw my head on a plate for you
Oh, yes I would
Jump in front of a train for you
Yeah, yeah, yeah
You know I'd do
You know I'd do anythging for you, baby
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I would go through all this pain
Take a bullet traight through my brain
Yes, I would die for you
Die for you
Die for you, baby
But you won't do the same
Won't do the same
No, you won't, baby
I try to love you, darlin
Yes, I've tried
And tried and tried and tried
Yes, I did, baby
Oh, yeah
One two
One, two, three
So you think I'm alone
But being alone's the only way to be
When you setp outside
You spend life fighting for your sanity
This is a cold war
You better know
What you're fighting for
This is a cold war
Do you know what you're fighting for
If you want to be free
Below the groud's the only place to be
Cause in this life
You spend life running from depravity
And this is a cold war
Do you know what you're fighting for
This is a cold war
This is a cold
This is a coooooold war
Do you know what you're fighting for
She said no
Do you know what is a cold cold war
Do you, do you, do you
Do you
It's a cold, cold war
You better know what you're fighting for
Yeah, that's right
Don't you cry
Wanna say good-bye
You got it, you got it bad
When you're on the phone
Hang up and you call right back
You got it, you got it bad
When you miss a day without your friend
Your whole life's off track
And you got it bad when you're stuck in the house
You don't wanna have fun
It's all you think about
Baby, baby, baby
I'm like baby, baby, baby
I thought you'd always be mine, mine
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Now I'm all gone, gone, gone
I'm gone
Never say never, never, never
I never thought they could walk through fire
Yeah, I never thought that I could take the burn
I never had the strength to take it higher
Until I reached the point of no return
And there's just no turning back
When your hearts under attack
Gonna give everything I have
I will never say never
I will fight
I will fight till forever
Make it right
Whenever you knock me down
I will not stay on the ground
Pick it up, pick it up
Pick it up, pick it up up up
And never say never
I will never say never
I will fight
I will fight till forever
Make it right
Whenever you knock me down
I will not stay on the ground
Pick it up, pick it up
Pick it up, pick it up up up
And never say never
J, guess who
J Smith and J.B.
I can handle him
Now he's bigger than me
Taller than me
And he's older than me
And stronger than me
And his arms a little bit longer than me
But he ain't on a J.B. song with me
I be trying a chill
They be trying to side with the thrill
No pun intended, was raised by the power of Will
Like Luke with the force
When push comes to shove
Like Cobe with the 4th, ice water with blood
I gotta be the best, and yes
We're the flyest
Like David and Goliath
I conquered the giant
So now I got the world in my hand
I was born from two stars
So the moon's where I land
I will never say never
I will fight
I will fight till forever
Make it right
Whenever you knock me down
I will not stay on the ground
Pick it up, pick it up
Pick it up, pick it up up up
And never say never
Oh, my gosh
Baby, let me love you down
There's so many ways to love ya
Baby, I can break ya down
Got me like "oh my god, I'm so in love"
I found you finally
You make me want to say
Oh,oh, oh, oh, oh,oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, baby, you got it all
Sexy from her head to the toes
And I wanna know, know, know
There's so many ways to love ya
Baby, I can break ya down
So many ways to love ya
Got me like "oh my god, I'm so in love"
I found you finally
You make me want to say
Oh,oh, oh, oh, oh,oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, my gosh
Oh, my
Oh, my, oh, my
Oh, my gosh
I did it again
so I'm gone let the beat drop
Oh, my gosh
Oh, oh, oh, my
My, my, my, my, my
Oh, my gosh
It's empty in the valley of your heart
The sun, it rises slowly
As you walk away
From all the fears and all the faults
You've left behind
The harvest left no food
For you to eat
You cannibal you meat eater you see
But I have seen the same
I know the shame in your defeat
But I will hold on hope
And I won't let you choke
On the noose around your neck
And I'll find strength in pain
And I will change my ways
Know my name as it's called again
Cause I have other things to fill my time
You take what is yours and I'll take mine
Now let me at the truth
Which will refresh my broken mind
So tie me to a post and block my ears
I can see widows and orphans through my tears
Know my call despite my faults
And despite my growing fears
So make your siren's call
And sing all you want
I will not hear what you have to say
Cause I need freedom now
And I need to know how
To live my life as it's meant to be
And I will hold on hope
And I won't let you choke
On the noose around your neck
And I'll find strength in pain
And I will change my ways
I'll know my name as it's called again
There's a darkness upon me that's flooded in light
In the fine print they tell me
What's wrong and what's right
And it comes in black and it comes in white
And I'm frightened by those who don't see it
When nothing is owed or deserved or expected
And your life doesn't change
By the man that's elected
If you're loved by someone
You're never rejected
Decide what to be and go be it
一起来
There was a dream
And one day I could see it
Like a bird in a cage I broke in
And demanded that somebody free it
And there was a kid
With a head full of doubt
So I'll scream till I die
And the last of those bad thoughts are finally out
There's a darkness upon you
That's flooded in light
And in the fine print they tell you
What's wrong and what's right
And it flies by day and it flies by night
And I'm frightened by those that don't see it
There was a dream
And one day I could see it
Like a bird in a cage I broke in
And demanded that somebody free it
And there was a kid
With a head full of doubt
So I'll scream till I die
And the last of those bad thoughts are finally out
There's a darkness upon me
That's flooded in light
In the fine print they tell me
What's wrong and what's right
I ain't gonna work on Maggie's farm no more
I wake up every morning
Hold my hands and pray for rain
I've got a head full of ideas
Driving me insane
It's a shame the way she makes me scrub the floor
Well, I ain't gonna work on Maggie's farm no more
I ain't gonna work for Maggie's brother no more
He hands you a nickel
He hands you a dime
He asks you and your friends
If you're having a good time
He blames you every time you slam the door
I ain't gonna work on Maggie's brother no more
Well, I ain't gonna work for Maggie's Pa no more
I ain't gonna work for Maggie's Pa no more
He stubs his cigarette out
In your face just for kicks
His bedroom window is made out of bricks
And the National Guard are standing at his door
Well, I ain't gonna work on Maggie's Pa no more
Well, I ain't gonna work for Maggie's ma no more
I ain't gonna work for Maggie's ma no more
She talks to all the servants
About man and God and law
And everybody tell me she's the brains behind Pa
She's sixty-eight, but claim's she's twenty-four
Well, I ain't gonna work on Maggie's farm no more
I ain't gonna work on Maggie's farm no more
I try so hard
To be just who I am
But everybody wants you to be just like them
They say "see, while you're playing I get bored"
I ain't gonna work on Maggie's farm no more
If you don't know me by now
You will never never never know me
She grow up on the side of the road
Where the church bells ring and strong love grows
She grew up good, she grew up slow
Like American honey
Steady as a preacher, free as a weed
Couldn't wait to get going
But wasn't quite ready to leave
So innocent pure and sweet
American Honey
There's a wild wild whisper blown in the wind
Callin' out my name like a long lost friend
Oh I miss those days as the years go by
Oh nothings sweeter than summertime
And American honey
It's a quarter after one, I'm all alone and I need you now
And I said I wouldn't call
But I'm a little drunk and I need you now
It's a quarter after one, I'm all alone and I need you now
Said I wouldn't call but I lost all control and I need you now
And I don't know how I can do without
I just need you now
I see you driving 'round town with the girl I love
And I'm like forget you
I guess the change in my pocket wasn't enough
And I'm like forget you, and forget her too
If I was richer, I'd still be with you
Ain't that some shhhh? (ain't that some shhhh?)
And although there's pain in my chest
Still wish you the best with a...forget you
Yeah I'm sorry, I can't afford a ferrari,
I guess she's an Xbox and I'm more Atari
But the way you play your game ain't fair.
I pity the fool that falls in love with you
(Oh oh she's a gold digger, just thought you should know)
I've got some news for you
Yeah go run and tell your little girlfriend
I see you driving 'round town with the girl I love
And I'm like forget you
I guess the change in my pocket wasn't enough
and I'm like forget you and forget her too
Said, if I was richer, I'd still be with ya
Ha, now ain't that some shhhh? (ain't that some shhhh?)
And although there's pain in my chest
I still wish you the best with a, forget you
Now I know that I had to borrow
Beg and steal and lie and cheat
Trying to keep you, trying to please you
Cause being in love with you ass ain't cheap
Now, I pity the fool that falls in love with you
(Oh oh she's a gold digger, just thought you should know)
I've got some news for you
Ooh! I really hate your ass right now
I hate you too
I see you driving 'round town with the girl I love
And I'm like forget you
I guess the change in my pocket wasn't enough
And I'm like forget you, and forget her too
If I was richer, I'd still be with you
Ain't that's shhhhh(ain't that's shhhhh)
And although there's pain in my chest
Still wish you the best with a...forget you
Now baby, baby, baby, why d'you wanna wanna hurt me so bad
So bad
I tried to tell my mama but she told me
This's one for your dad
And I was like
Why
Why baby
I love you
I still love you
I see you driving 'round town with the guy I love
And I'm like forget you
I guess the change in my pocket wasn't enough
I'm like forget you
And forget her too
Said if I was richer
I'd still be with ya
Now ain't that some shh
And although there's pain in my chest
I still wish you the best
With a forget you
He put it on me
I put in on
There was nothing wrong it didn't fit
It wasn't right
Wasn't just the size
They say you know when you know
I don't know
I didn't feel
The fairy tale feeling
No am I a stupid girl
For even dreaming that I could
If it's not like the movies
That's why it should be, yeah
When he's the one, I'll come undone
And your world will stop spinning
And that's just the beginning
'Cause I know you're out there
And you're looking for me
It's crazy idea that
That you were made perfectly for me
You'll see
Just like the movies
That's how it will be
Cinematic and dramatic with the perfect ending
It's not like the movies
But that's how it should be
When he's the one
You'll come undone
And your world will stop spinning
And it's just the beginning
Cause you make me feel like I'm living a teenage dream
The way you turn me on
I can't sleep
Let's run away
And don't ever look back
Don't ever look back
My heart stops
When you look at me
Just one touch
Now baby I believe
This is real
So take a chance
And don't ever look back
Don't ever look back
I might get your heart racing
In my skin-tight jeans
Be your teenage dream tonight
Let you put your hands on me
In my skin-tight jeans
Be your teenage dream tonight
Cause you make me feel like I'm living a teenage dream
The way you turn me on
I can't sleep
Let's runaway
And don't ever look back
Don't ever look back
My heart stops
When you look at me
Just one touch
Now baby I believe
This is real
So take a chance
And don't ever look back
Don't ever look back
I might get your heart racing
In my skin-tight jeans
Be your teenage dream tonight
Let you put your hands on me
In my skin-tight jeans
Be your teenage dream tonight
Jolene, Jolene, Jolene, Jolene
Im begging of you please don't take my man
Please don't take him just because you can
Her beauty is beyond compare
With flaming locks of auburn hair
With ivory skin and eyes of emerald green
Her smile is like a breath of spring
Voice is soft like summer rain
And I cannot compete with her, Jolene
Jolene, Jolene, Jolene, Jolene
Im begging of you please don't take my man
Please don't take him just because you can
Jolene
On the first page of our story
The future seemed so bright
Then this thing turned out so evil
I don't know why I'm still surprised
Even angels have their wicked schemes
And you take that to new extremes
But you'll always be my hero
Even though you lost your mind
Just gonna stand there and watch me burn
But that's alright because I like the way it hurts
Just gonna stand there and hear me cry
But that's alright because I love the way you lie
I love the way you lie
Ohhh, I love the way you lie
So maybe I'm a masochist
I try to run, but I don't wanna ever leave
Till the walls are goin' up
In smoke with all our memories
It's morning, you wake, a sunray hits your face
Smeared makeup as we lay in the wake of destruction
Hush baby, speak softly, tell me you're awfully sorry
That you pushed me into the coffee table last night
So I can push you off me
Try and touch me so I can scream at you not to touch me
Run out the room and I'll follow you like a lost puppy
Baby, without you, I'm nothing, I'm so lost, hug me
Then tell me how ugly I am, but that you'll always love me
Then after that, shove me, in the aftermath of the
Destructive path that we're on, two psychopaths but we
Know that no matter how many knives we put in each other's backs
That we'll have each other's backs, 'cause we're that lucky
Together, we move mountains, let's not make mountains out of molehills
You hit me twice, yeah, but who's countin'
I may have hit you three times, I'm startin' to lose count
But together, we'll live forever, we found the youth fountain
Our love is crazy, we're nuts, but I refused counsellin'
This house is too huge, if you move out I'll burn all two thousand
Square feet of it to the ground, ain't shit you can do about it
With you I'm in my f-ckin' mind, without you, I'm out it
Just gonna stand there and hear me cry
But that's all right because I love the way you lie
I love the way you lie
I'm about to lose my mind
You've been gone for so long
I'm running out of time
I need a doctor
Call me a doctor
I need a doctor, doctor
To bring me back to life
I told the world, one day I would pay it back
Say it on tape and lay it, record it, so that one day I could play it back
But I don't even know if I believe it when I'm saying that
Doubt startin' to creep in, everyday it's just so grey and black
Hope, I just need a ray of that
'Cause no one sees my vision
When I play it for 'em, they just say it's wack
But they don't know what dope is
And I don't know if I was awake or asleep when I wrote this
All I know is you came to me when I was at my lowest
You picked me up, breathed new life in me. I owe my life to you
Before the life of me, I don't see why you don't see like I do
But it just dawned on me; you lost a son. See this light in you? It's dark
Let me turn on the lights and brighten me and enlighten you
I don't think you realize what you mean to me, not the slightest clue
'Cause me and you, we're like a crew. I was like your sidekick
You gon' either wanna fight when I get off this f-cking mic
Or you gon' hug me. But I'm out of options, there's nothing else I can do cause
I'm about to lose my mind
You've been gone for so long
I'm running out of time
I need a doctor
Call me a doctor
I need a doctor, doctor
To bring me back to life
It hurts when I see you struggle
You come to me with ideas
You say that these are pieces, so I'm puzzled
'Cause the sh-t I hear is crazy
But you're either getting lazy, or you don't believe in you no more
Seems like your own opinions, not one you can form
Can't make a decision, you keep questioning yourself
Second guessing, and it's almost like your begging for my help
Like, I'm YOUR leader
You're supposed to freaking be MY mentor
I can endure no more
I demand you remember who you are
It was you, who believed in me
When everyone was telling you, don't sign me
Everyone at the freaking label, lets tell the truth
You risked your career for me, I know it as well as you
Nobody wanted to f-ck with the white boy
Dre, I'm crying in this booth
You saved my life, now maybe it's my time to save yours
But I can never repay you, what you did for me is way more
But I ain't giving up faith, and you ain't giving up on me
Get up Dre! I'm dying, I need you, come back for f-ck's sake
I'm about to lose my mind
You've been gone for so long
I'm running out of time
I need a doctor
Call me a doctor
I need a doctor, doctor
女士们先生们  Dr. Dre
It literally feels like a lifetime ago
But I still remember the sh-t like it was just yesterday though
You walked in, yellow jump suit
Whole room, cracked jokes
Once you got inside the booth, told you, like smoke
Went through friends, some of them I put on
But they just left, they said was riding to the death
But where are they now
Now that I need them, I don't see none of them
All I see is Slim f-ck all you fairweather friends
All I need is him
F-cking backstabbers
When the chips were down, you just laughed at us
Now you bout to feel the f-cking wrath of aftermath, damn it
You gon' see us in our lab jackets
And ask where the hell we been
You can kiss my indecisive ass crack maggots
And the crackers ass
Little cracker jack beat making whack math
Backwards producers, I'm back bastards
One more CD and then I'm packing up my bags
And as I leave and I guarantee they'll scream
Dre don't leave us like that man, 'cause
I'm about to lose my mind
I need a doctor doctor
To bring me back to life
Everybody wants somebody
Everybody needs somebody to love
Someone to love
Someone to kiss
Someone to miss
I need you, you, you
Someone to please
Sometimes tease
Sometimes miss
Sometimes kiss
I need you, you, you
Sometimes I feel like
A little sad inside
My baby mistreats me
And I kinda get a little bit mad
I need you, you, you
To see me through
When the sun goes down
Ain't nobody else around
I need you baby
I need you so bad
I need you bad, baby
I need you, you, you
I need you
I need you baby
I need you so bad
I need you love it
I need you baby
I need you, you, you
When the sun goes down
Ain't nobody else around
I need you sugar
I need you so bad
I need you baby
I need you sugar
I need you so bad
I need you baby
You're the best thing
You've got that baby
I need
You
I need you baby
I need you so bad
I need you sugar
I need you, you, you
I need
You
Love
Soft as an easy chair
Fresh as the morning air
One love that is shared by two
I have found with you
Like a rose under the April snow
I was always certain love would grow
Love
Ageless and evergreen
Seldom seen by two
You and I will make each night a first
And every day a beginning
Spirits rise
And their dance is unrehearsed
They warm and excite us
Cause we have the brightest love
Two lights that shine as one
Morning glory and midnight sun
Time, we've learned to
sail above
Time
can't change the meaning
of one love
Ageless and ever
evergreen
Oh, so evergreen
Ooh na na, what's my name
What's my name, what's my name
I heard you good with them soft lips
Yeah you know word of mouth
The square root of 69 is 8 something right
Cause I've been tryna work it out, oooow
Good weed, white wine
I come alive in the night time
Okay, away we go
Only thing we have on is the radio
Ooooh, let it play, say you gotta leave
But I know you wanna stay
You just waiting on the traffic jam to finish girl
The things we could do in twenty minutes girl
Say my name, say my name
Wear it out, its getting hot, crack a window, air it out
I can get you through a mighty long day
Soon as you go the text that I write is gonna say
Not everybody knows how to work my body
Knows how to make me want it
But boy you stay up on it
You got that something
That keeps me so off balance
Baby you're a challenge
Lets explore your talent
Hey boy, I really wanna see if you can go long time
With a girl like me
Hey boy, I really wanna be with you
Cause you just my type
Ooh na na na na
I need a boy to take it over
Looking for a guy to put in work, uh
Oooooh, oooooh
You're so amazing
You took the time to figure me out
That's why you take me
Way past the point of turning me on
You bout to break me
I swear you got me losing my mind
一起唱
Ooh na na
Hey boy, I really wanna see if you can go long time
With a girl like me
Hey boy, I really wanna be with you
Cause you just my type
Ooh na na na na
I need a boy to take it over
Looking for a guy to put in work, uh
Oooooh, oooooh
Hey boy, I really wanna see if you can go long time
With a girl like me
Hey boy, I really wanna be with you
Cause you just my type
Ooh na na na na
I need a boy to take it over
Looking for a guy to put in work, uh
Oooooh, oooooh
One, two, three, four
Gonna make a record in the month of May
In the month of May
When the violent wind
Blows the wires away
Month of May, it's a violent thing
In the city, their hearts start to sing
Well, some people singing
Sounds like screaming
Used to doubt it buy now I believe it
Month of May, everybody's in love
In the city, watch it from above and
Just when I knew what I wanted to say
The violent wind blew the wires away
We were shocked in the suburbs
Kids are all standing
With their arms folded tight
Well, some things are pure
And some things are right
But the kids are still standing
With their arms folded tight
Well, some things are pure
And some things are right
But the kids are still standing
With their arms folded tight
So young
So much pain for someone so young well
I know it's heavy I know it ain't light
But how you gonna lift with your arms
Folded
First, they built the road
Then they built the town
That's why we're still driving around
And around and around and around
And around and around
Two thousand and nine
Two thousand and ten
Wanna make a record how I felt then
When I stood outside in the month of May
Watched the violent wind
Blow the wires away
If I died in the month of May
Let the wind take my body away, well
I wish I may, I wish I might
Make me down there with my arms
Folded
Start again in the month of May
Come on and blow the wires away
Come on and blow the wires
The wires away
If the businessmen drink my blood
like the kids in art school says they would
And I guess I'll just begin again
You say can we still be friends
If I was scared
I would
And if I was bored
You know I would
And if I was yours
But I'm not
All the kids have always known
That the emperor wears no clothes
But bow to down to them anyway
It's better than to be alone
If I was scared
I would
And if I was pure
You know I would
And if I was yours
But I'm not
Now you're knocking at my door
Saying please come out against the night
But I would rather be alone
Than pretend I feel alright
If the businessmen drink my blood
Like the kids in art school said they would
Then I guess I'll just begin again
You say can we still be friends
If I was scared
I would
And if I was pure
You know I would
And if I was yours
But I'm not
Now I'm ready to start
If I was scared
I would
If I was pure